https://customautotrim.com/cmspages/display/privacy-policy/

X
800.232.6922
858-273-5700(Outside US)
Interior Accessories +
Interior Accessories
Blackout Tape
Matte black tape covers up worn areas like consoles, gauge faces, door panels, etc.
Blackout Tape
Matte black tape covers scratched window frames and other trim.
Cross Bars
Cross Bars Only. Upgrades your load capacity, attaches to your factory rails.
Custom-Fit Graphics
Stripe kits and graphics custom-fit to your vehicle.
Door Edge Molding
Protects Door Edges and other Surface Edges
Fender Flares
Covers wheel well openings. Factory Style or Extended Width Fender Flares.
Rear Window Graphics
See-thru window graphics and window screen decals.
Rivet-on Molding
Aluminum rivet-on channel molding,vinyl color inserts and end tips
Specialty Pinstripes
Special-design pinstripes and emblems.
Truck Bed Rails
Stake pocket mount and drill mount side bed rails available in many styles
Chrome Rocker Panels
Add chrome to Lower Door and Body, Vehicle-Specific-Fit Kits
Blackout Tape
Matte black tape to wrap door handles, light bezels, emblems, etc.
Custom-Fit Graphics
Racing stripes and graphics custom-fit to your vehicle.
Rear Window Graphics
See-thru Rear Window Decals and window screen decals.
Specialty Pinstripes
Specialty pinstripes and emblems.
Vinyl Wrap
Carbon Fiber, Wood Grain and other Finishes for your wrapping project
Blackout Tape
Matte black tape covers up worn areas like consoles, gauge faces, door panels, etc.
Blackout Tape
Matte black tape covers scratched window frames and other trim.
Cross Bars
Cross Bars Only. Upgrades your load capacity, attaches to your factory rails.
Custom-Fit Graphics
Stripe kits and graphics custom-fit to your vehicle.
Door Edge Molding
Protects Door Edges and other Surface Edges
Fender Flares
Covers wheel well openings. Factory Style or Extended Width Fender Flares.
Rear Window Graphics
See-thru window graphics and window screen decals.
Rivet-on Molding
Aluminum rivet-on channel molding,vinyl color inserts and end tips
Specialty Pinstripes
Special-design pinstripes and emblems.
Truck Bed Rails
Stake pocket mount and drill mount side bed rails available in many styles
Chrome Rocker Panels
Add chrome to Lower Door and Body, Vehicle-Specific-Fit Kits
Blackout Tape
Matte black tape to wrap door handles, light bezels, emblems, etc.
Custom-Fit Graphics
Racing stripes and graphics custom-fit to your vehicle.
Rear Window Graphics
See-thru Rear Window Decals and window screen decals.
Specialty Pinstripes
Specialty pinstripes and emblems.
Vinyl Wrap
Carbon Fiber, Wood Grain and other Finishes for your wrapping project
General
Custom Auto Trim and Graphics Inc. respects the privacy of every individual who visits our website. This Privacy Statement outlines the information Custom Auto Trim and Graphics Inc. will collect and how we will use that information. Please note, the privacy practices described in the Privacy Statement apply only to Custom Auto Trim and Graphics websites that are directed to residents of the United States. If you link to other Custom Auto Trim and Graphics sites please review the privacy policies posted at those sites.
Personally Identifiable Information
When you visit Custom Auto Trim and Graphics' websites or advertisements,
we will not collect any personally identifiable information about you
(such as your name, address, telephone number, billing and shipping information, credit card information or e-mail address) ,
unless you provide it to us voluntarily . If you opt not to provide us with personally identifiable information no material consequences will result, although you may be unable to receive product information or buy products offered through Custom Auto Trim and Graphics' websites. The copy, claims and offers contained in this website are directed at residents of the United States and are valid only in the United States.
Non-Personally Identifiable Information Collected Automatically
In some cases, we may collect information about you that is not personally identifiable. Examples of this type of information include the type of Internet browser or computer operating system you are using and the domain name of the website from which you linked to our site or advertisement. In addition, when you view one of our websites or advertisements, we may store some information on your computer. This information will be in the form of a "cookie" or similar file and will help us in many ways. For example, cookies allow us to keep track of your shopping cart, or tailor a website or advertisement to better match your interests and preferences in order to make a better experience for you in our store. Most Internet browsers enable you to erase cookies from your computer hard drive, block all cookies, or receive a warning before a cookie is stored. Custom Auto Trim and Graphics Inc. does not collect personally identifiable information automatically.
Use of Personally Identifiable Information
Custom Auto Trim and Graphics Inc. may store and process your personally identifiable information to better understand your needs and how we may improve our products and services, and we may use your personally identifiable information to contact you (for example, we may respond to your comments or requests for information, or we may contact you if needed in the course of processing or shipping your order for products or services offered over our web sites). Custom Auto Trim and Graphics, Inc. does not give or sell personally identifiable information to any outside organizations. We DO NOT share any information.
Security
Custom Auto Trim and Graphics Inc. is committed to keeping secure the data you provide us and will take reasonable precautions including the latest encryption methods to protect your personally identifiable information from loss, misuse or alteration. Agents or contractors of Custom Auto Trim and Graphics Inc. who have access to your personally identifiable information in connection with providing services for Custom Auto Trim and Graphics Inc. are required to keep the information confidential and are not permitted to use this information for any other purpose than to carry out the services they are performing for Custom Auto Trim and Graphics Inc.
Direct Mailings and "Opting Out"
We may send you information about various products and services from time to time if you have subscribed to our newsletters and ezines. You are never automatically added to an email list of any kind. Our newsletters and ezines that we are offering are free by subscription only, and the subscriber's names and email addresses are never sold or rented to any person or company. We will only use the information to deliver to you your subscribed ezines and newsletters. If you don't want to receive this information any longer, you can "opt out" at any time by following the removal instructions located at the bottom of every ezine and newsletter that we publish, or by sending us an email at webmaster@customautotrim.com and requesting that you not receive any more of these of these offers.
Public Forums
This site makes forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.
Third Party Cookies
In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique &#34cookie" on your browser.
Contacting the Web Site
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact: webmaster@customautotrim.com
Contact Info
Contact Us
About Us
Order Status
Customer Service
General Info
FAQ'S
Ordering Info
800.232.6922
858-273-5700(Outside US)
AUTOMEGA ® is a registered trademark of Custom Auto Trim and Graphics, Inc. COPYRIGHT ©1996 - 2020.Custom Auto Trim and Graphics Inc. All rights reserved.
CONTACT US
x
We want to hear your feedback! Please send us an email using the form below
CONTACT US
